<?xml version="1.0"?>
<blog>
	<post title="How the Web has Changed the Way We Buy Music [Infographic]" date="September 27, 2010">
		<content><a href="http://www.inspiredm.com/2010/09/27/how-the-web-has-changed-the-way-we-buy-music-infographic/">Source</a>
			Through iTunes, Apple has the credit card details of 160 million people. You might want to take a second to think about the enormity of that statement.

			Steve Jobs' empire has become one of the most important players in the music industry over the past ten years with the introduction and evolution of the iPod.

			The digital music revolution has seen a monumental shift from physical sales to digital downloads, with Apple taking a huge slice of the market.

			Here's an infographic with just a few statistics on how we buy music today, highlighting the decline in physical sales and the increase in music consumption via mobile internet.
			<img title="music-buying-infographic" src="http://www.inspiredm.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/music-buying-infographic.jpg" alt="infographic" width="500" height="714" />
			As you can see, according to digitalmusicnews.com (September 2010), nearly 12 billion songs have now been downloaded from iTunes. If we assume the average MP3 file size is 6mb, this amounts to a colossal 72, 000, 000, 000Mb of data.

			According to the British Phonographic Industry, as cited by Mediatel in August 2010, 98 per cent of singles sold are now bought digitally, with physical sales accounting for just 2 per cent.

			Data from Ipsos Media CT, as cited by Mediatel in the same month showed that in the last 12 months, a third of UK adults aged between 15 and 50-years-old had paid to download music from an official site.

			Other stats show that 36 per cent of UK YouTube users have bought a CD after watching a video on the site, 64 per cent of US iPhone users have downloaded music from their handset and that in the UK, and digital music sales grew by 32 per cent from 2008-09. Not bad, ha?
		</content>
	</post>
	<post title="Numbers Man" date="September 29th, 2010">
		<content>
			<a href="http://www.behance.net/gallery/Numbers_man/727026">By Tariq Yosef</a>
			<img alt="Numbers Man" src="http://behance.vo.llnwd.net/profiles/57046/projects/727026/c98e27888301e31ccd023850b07b7eb2.jpg" />
		</content>
	</post>
	<post title="The 2010 Social Networking Map" date="August 5, 2010">
		<content>
			<a href="http://www.flowtown.com/blog/the-2010-social-networking-map">From flowtown.com</a>
			<img src="http://www.flowtown.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2010/08/Social-Network-MapCS3.png" alt="social networking map" />
		</content>
	</post>
	<post title="The Current State of Twitter" date="June 3, 2010">
		<content>
			<a href="http://mashable.com/2010/03/18/twitter-infographic/">Mashable infographic</a> <img src="http://cdn.mashable.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/03/1bntweets3.jpg" alt="infographic" />
		</content>
	</post>
	<post title="Bing vs Google: A Usability Face-Off" date="September 30, 2010">
		<content>
			<a href="http://webdesignledger.com/tips/bing-vs-google-a-usability-face-off">Bing vs Google: A Usability Face-Off by Jacob Creech</a><br />We all know Google and Bing, and probably use one or both of them on more or less a daily basis. Search results are generally the defining factor that makes us have a good experience, and I suspect most of us don't give too much consideration to the usability of the services.
			<img alt="bing vs google" src="http://webdesignledger.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/bing_vs_google.jpg" />
			<img alt="bing vs google" src="http://webdesignledger.com/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/q1.jpg" />
		</content>
	</post>
	<post title="Dollar Bill Origami" date="October 1, 2010">
		<content>
			<a href="http://www.noupe.com/inspiration/beautiful-origami-art-made-of-dollars-by-won-park.html">Beautiful Origami Art Made Of Dollars by Won Park</a>
			<img src="http://th00.deviantart.net/fs71/PRE/f/2010/190/6/8/Two_Dollar_Formula_1_Racecar_by_orudorumagi11.jpg" width="600" alt="origami" />
			<img src="http://fc06.deviantart.net/fs16/f/2007/157/1/4/One_Dollar_jet_by_orudorumagi11.jpg" alt="origami" />
		</content>
	</post>
	<post title="Darth Dream: Up All Night (All Chicken Remix)" date="October 1, 2010">
		<content>
			<div class="audio_player">
				<embed type="application/x-shockwave-flash" src="http://alegacy.tumblr.com/swf/audio_player.swf?audio_file=http://www.tumblr.com/audio_file/1224777902/tumblr_l9myfvmDFA1qz9pjk&amp;color=FFFFFF" height="27" width="207" quality="best" />
			</div>
			In Place Of Kanye (Who Still Might Drop) G.O.O.D. Fridays, I Did A Remix Of Drake &amp; Nicki Minaj's Song "Up All Night"

			Because Kanye's Joints Are Wildly Popular And My Boy Yung Chad Does His Thing (Ash Wednesday) On Wednesdays, I've Decided To Put Myself Right In The Middle And Drop A New Track Every Week, Aptly Titled: "Thirsty Thursdays"

			I Hope You Enjoy.

			Lyrics:

			Verse 1:

			Kush Rolled, Glass Full, I Prefer Some Chicken Wings
			Niggas With No Chicken Act Like Chicken Isn't Everything
			I'm Having A Good Time, They Just Tryna Ruin It
			I Don't Want It Fried, That's Why I'm Back Here BBQn It
			Grill On, Top Down, Shake/Bake, Everytime
			She Ain't Tryna Get That Chicken Kickin' Well Then Nevermind
			I-I-I-I Tried To Tell You KFC Ain't Nothing Nice
			Church's Sayin' You Should Quit
			Popeye's Sayin' Fuck Your Life.
			OK, Now We Outta Here, Toodles To Your Chicken
			And If You're Italian, I Put Them Noodles With Yo Chicken, YEAH
			I'm Busy Cookin' Shit. Tryna Stay Humble,
			I Made Enough For Two Dinners, And Some Lunchables
			Chicken Is A Drug, That I Can't Get Enough Of,
			And I Never Stay Awake, Cause The ITIS Is Too Much,
			I Got Hot Sauce In These Jeans, Just In Case You Ain't Get None
			Son, My Chicken Gets It Poppin' Nigga This Is What I Does, AHH.

			Chorus:

			I'm About Whatever Man/Fuck What They Be Talking Bout/Put This Chicken In Your Mouth/You Won't Wanna Take It Out/NoOoOoOoOo/You Can't Do It Like We Do It/Grilled/Fried/Boiled/We Can Even BBQ It/I Be Up All Night/Whole Crew's In Here/[This] Finger Lickin' Chicken/And Some Booze In Here/oOoOoOoOo/Man I'd Love Some Greens/And Some Mac 'N Cheese/To Go Nice With My Chicken/oOoOoOoOo

			Verse 2:

			If Vinny Says Get Her, Then You Get Her
			We Got That Kind Of Chicken, Makin' Turkey Bacon Bitter
			We Got That Kind Of [W-W-Wait, Wait,] Fixate
			Which Bitch You Know [Is] Eatin' Chicken Off Of This Plate
			Chicken Is A Keep Sake
			Bought The President Official Presidential  Cheap Plates
			For Chicken On A Cheap Date
			We Call 'Em Hawks, When We Eat Them In The Peach State
			Man, For Pete's Sake, Chicken Tastes Great.
			[Ah Ha Ha Ha Ha]
			Fuck It Look Like Yo?
			My Chicken? YES
			Your Chicken? NO.
			We Keep Them Bad Birds, But We Never Ever Mix Breeds,
			Fuck A Diet, Eatin' Fried Chicken With Some Chick Peas.
			And I Save Some For My Friends Too,
			I See A Lot Of Bad Chicken On The Menu
			So I Make Sure To Put It Down With Some Lentil,
			And Pop Bottles With My Team
			Eatin' Chicken Til The Death Of Me.

			Chorus:

			I'm About Whatever Man/Fuck What They Be Talking Bout/Put This Chicken In Your Mouth/You Won't Wanna Take It Out/NoOoOoOoOo/You Can't Do It Like We Do It/Grilled/Fried/Boiled/We Can Even BBQ It/I Be Up All Night/Whole Crew's In Here/[This] Finger Lickin' Chicken/And Some Booze In Here/oOoOoOoOo/Man I'd Love Some Greens/And Some Mac 'N Cheese/To Go Nice With My Chicken/oOoOoOoOo

			Bridge:

			I mean, we can't even eat that chicken if it don't got 'Purdue' near the price tag, you know?, I mean, I mean, but then again, who-who-who looks at brands like that? you know?
			Chicken up in this bitch/OH/OH/OH/chicken up in this bitch/Oh/OH/OH.

			Chorus:

			I'm About Whatever Man/Fuck What They Be Talking Bout/Put This Chicken In Your Mouth/You Won't Wanna Take It Out/NoOoOoOoOo/You Can't Do It Like We Do It/Grilled/Fried/Boiled/We Can Even Bbq It/I Be Up All Night/Whole Crew's In Here/[This] Finger Lickin' Chicken/And Some Booze In Here/oOoOoOoOo/Man I'd Love Some Greens/And Some Mac 'N Cheese/To Go Nice With My Chicken/oOoOoOoOo [X2]
		</content>
	</post>
	<post title="Wordpress!" date="July 25, 2010">
		<content>
			My first time installing WordPress. I think it's going pretty good so far! I'm using wp as the backend and doing the frontend myself. I'm also trying to use MySQLi instead of MySQL.
		</content>
	</post>
	<post title="Can't Decide!" date="July 29, 2010">
		<content>
			I don't know if I want to use WordPress for the front end too and make my own theme when I've already made my website theme. Kinda want to though. Then I can use the permalinks and all that other good stuff.

			Tomorrow is my last day for my internship with Rokkan in New York City. I'm stoked to get home!
		</content>
	</post>
	<post title="And now it's all hooked up" date="July 30, 2010">
		<content>
			<h3>I decided =)</h3>
			I Just finished linking together the rest of the site with the new WordPress blog! I ended up copying the default Twenty Ten theme directory, renaming it, and doing some editing to get it to look like the rest of my site.
			<h3>Inception</h3>
			<img src="http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4133/4832386029_f1a5d76812.jpg" alt="Inception" />
			<cite>By <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jordan_a/4832386029/">Jordan A on Flickr</a></cite>

			For those of you who haven't seen Inception. I highly recommend it. I loved it.
			<h3>Space Invader Couch!</h3>
			<a href="http://www.mymodernmet.com/profiles/blogs/space-invaders-couch-5-pics"><img class="alignnone" title="Space invader couch" src="http://api.ning.com/files/52DAl4oSffEXfFQCKaR4jMQW6LF7Xc-CKQlN9zeycCmp5ajoMcUZabQravYQSoNdvC9ItIAnOY7ZH8s23IWNqYq27*ESrO3*/SpaceInvaderCouch4.jpg" alt="" width="580" height="580" /></a>
		</content>
	</post>
	<post title="Time's Flyin'" date="August 15, 2010">
		<content>
			Been back in Corvallis for two weeks now, man time is flying. I've only got two weeks left until it's back to school. The family and I went to Lincoln city this weekend with the Schwarzs. Played some lacrosse on the beach and had a fire with smores.
		</content>
	</post>

</blog>